<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Erica Hollis&apos; Portfolio</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/" />
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/atom.xml" />
    <id>tag:www.personal.psu.edu,2010-08-19:/erh5000/blogs/portfolio//31529</id>
    <updated>2010-11-30T05:01:07Z</updated>
    
    <generator uri="http://www.sixapart.com/movabletype/">Movable Type Pro 4.34-en</generator>

<entry>
    <title>Last Prompt</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/11/last-prompt.html" />
    <id>tag:www.personal.psu.edu,2010:/erh5000/blogs/portfolio//31529.319012</id>

    <published>2010-11-30T04:21:08Z</published>
    <updated>2010-11-30T05:01:07Z</updated>

    <summary>This is the last blog prompt for the English 202C technical writing course. I have never blogged before and have enjoyed expressing my opinions about different topics. Since our class has been selected to be part of an iPad research...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Erica Hollis</name>
        
    </author>
    
    <category term="engl202c_ipad" label="Engl202c_ipad" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/">
        <![CDATA[<p>This is the last blog prompt for the English 202C technical writing course.  I have never blogged before and have enjoyed expressing my opinions about different topics.  Since our class has been selected to be part of an iPad research project, the blog post topics were often about different iPad features and topics.  This has been a great way to evaluate and ponder topics as the pros and cons of Pages, tips for using the iPad, and critiques of iPad apps.  Because of this, the end of semester iPad report was much easier to write, making the class an effective iPad research project.  </p>

<p>I have learned many useful skills in the technical writing course.  I had never written a cover letter before and was dreading it, but now I feel much more confident in my ability to write a great resume and cover letter when applying for a job after graduation.  I have learned many other technical writing skills that will benefit me in my career, such as writing instruction sets, memos, and reports.  Some aspects of writing that I have greatly improved on is analyzing the audience, writing clearly, and writing with a specific purpose.</p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>iPad Report</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/11/ipad-report.html" />
    <id>tag:www.personal.psu.edu,2010:/erh5000/blogs/portfolio//31529.308721</id>

    <published>2010-11-09T00:03:50Z</published>
    <updated>2010-11-09T03:36:40Z</updated>

    <summary>I will use this blog post to post some thoughts about the iPad report. This is a report that I will write to describe some of my experiences with the iPad this semester. I will talk here about my experiences...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Erica Hollis</name>
        
    </author>
    
    <category term="engl202c_ipad" label="Engl202c_ipad" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/">
        <![CDATA[<p>I will use this blog post to post some thoughts about the iPad report.  This is a report that I will write to describe some of my experiences with the iPad this semester. I will talk here about my experiences with the internet in general.</p>

<p>The iPad is convenient for on the go internet browsing.  It is lightweight and therefore extremely portable.  It turns on almost immediately, which is very convenient.  There are a few downsides, though.  Most web pages are compatible, but some, such as Angel, are not.  Angel is a course management system used by Penn State.  I tried to look at PDF homework directions which were embedded in Angel, and could not scroll down to see the whole page.</p>

<p>Furthermore, in my experience the wifi signal in the iPad is weak.  I've tried to use the iPad in classes to follow along with lectures or look things up related to the lecture, but often have trouble getting a signal.  Other students on laptops do not have this problem.  As far as a workplace environment is concerned, many offices do not use wireless internet.  Other apps could be used in a workplace environment, but many apps require internet access.</p>

<p>I use Hotmail for email.  I use this for the 'mail' icon at the bottom of the iPad.  The 'mail' icon is an app that allows you to sync your email account to the format of this app.  The format is laid out with a main screen to view emails and a left hand bar that allows to to scroll through emails.</p>

<p><span class="mt-enclosure mt-enclosure-image" style="display: inline;"><a href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/assets_c/2010/11/nat2-158931.html" onclick="window.open('http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/assets_c/2010/11/nat2-158931.html','popup','width=1024,height=768,scrollbars=no,resizable=no,toolbar=no,directories=no,location=no,menubar=no,status=no,left=0,top=0'); return false">View image</a></span></p>

<p>I am disappointed with this because when I delete email on the iPad, it only gets deleted on the iPad mail app, not anywhere else.  Also, you can not access your contact list or folders besides inbox, drafts, sent or trash. <br />
</p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>iPad - pros and cons</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/11/ipad---pros-and-cons.html" />
    <id>tag:www.personal.psu.edu,2010:/erh5000/blogs/portfolio//31529.306399</id>

    <published>2010-11-02T02:29:48Z</published>
    <updated>2010-11-11T16:57:52Z</updated>

    <summary>There are several aspects that stand out about my experiences with the iPad.It is very convenient in many ways, but doesn&apos;t compare to a computer in others. The iPad is very convenient to carry around school. I stopped carrying my...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Erica Hollis</name>
        
    </author>
    
    <category term="engl202c_ipad" label="Engl202c_ipad" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/">
        <![CDATA[<p>There are several aspects that stand out about my experiences with the iPad.<br />It is very convenient in many ways, but doesn't compare to a computer in others.  <br /><br />The iPad is very convenient to carry around school.  I stopped carrying my laptop in my book bag because it was too heavy.  But in some classes, being able to use  the internet in class is very helpful.  That's when I use the iPad.<br /><br />Another thing I use the iPad for is the calendar.  Last semester I tried used a daily planner to keep track of assignments.  I've been using the iPad calendar for a few weeks and feel much more organized.  It is very convenient to whip the calendar out and add an assignment or other task.  Then you can view the task easily month  by month, and then double click the particular day to view the details.<br /><br />As far as writing with the iPad goes, there are pros and cons.  For example, it's easy to put shapes and graphics in any location using Pages on the iPad, while when using Microsoft word it can be a pain to get the graphic in the spot you want. But, obviously, Microsoft Word has many more features than Pages on the iPad does.  Overall, I prefer to use Microsoft Word to type documents, but using Pages on the iPad is manageable, especially after you get used to it and when using the external keyboard.<br /><br /><br />- Posted using BlogPress from my iPad<br /><br /></p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Review of the &quot;How to Track Animals&quot; video</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/10/review-of-the-how-to-track-animals-video.html" />
    <id>tag:www.personal.psu.edu,2010:/erh5000/blogs/portfolio//31529.303825</id>

    <published>2010-10-26T02:16:30Z</published>
    <updated>2010-10-26T02:50:13Z</updated>

    <summary>The instructional video &quot;How to Track Animals&quot; by Luke Neumann on howcast.com, track animals, has good and bad points. The video does not give much new information about tracking to anyone who has seen Lord of the Rings. I have...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Erica Hollis</name>
        
    </author>
    
    <category term="engl202c_ipad" label="Engl202c_ipad" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/">
        <![CDATA[<p>The instructional video "How to Track Animals" by Luke Neumann on howcast.com, <a href="http://www.howcast.com/videos/420312-How-to-Track-Animals">track animals</a>, has good and bad points.</p>

<p><span class="mt-enclosure mt-enclosure-image" style="display: inline;"><a href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/track.jpg"><img alt="track.jpg" src="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/assets_c/2010/10/track-thumb-200x112-156645.jpg" width="200" height="112" class="mt-image-right" style="float: right; margin: 0 0 20px 20px;" /></a></span></p>

<p>The video does not give much new information about tracking to anyone who has seen Lord of the Rings.  I have never tracked any animals and was hoping to learn some interesting facts.  Unfortunately, the only new information I learned was in step 6, "Figure out where the animal is going. Place popsicle sticks at the heel of the tracks and tape string between them to establish the line of travel... the lagging foot is dominant, indicating that an animal will often circle in that direction."  Other than this, the video states to examine scat and to compare it to a field manual.  The part about comparing it to a field manual is helpful, but another step about measuring tracks does not state why or what to do with the measurements.</p>

<p>The webpage has written instructions below the video, which could be useful if the viewer wished to read a certain step without rewatching the video. The video also has a good visual guide.  It starts by stating what tools are needed for the task, which is helpful.  Each instructions flashes on the screen while the announcer reads it.  This is good because it reinforces each instruction visually and audibly.  It shows a man examining scat, along with a helpful tip to use gloves and a stick.  This tip is highlighted in the written instruction with a green arrow and blue highlighting.  This is well done, although i wonder if it should be labeled "caution" because it is a health issue.  The video shows the man examining an animal track and ends with him spotting his target.</p>

<p>Overall, the visual aspect of the video is well done and the instructions are simple and easy to follow.  On the other hand, the instructions should be more advanced and less obvious, and the instructions should point the viewer towards where to get further resources.  I felt like this video was not extremely informative, but does give a starting point for animal tracking.</p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Tips for using the iPad</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/10/tips-for-using-the-ipad.html" />
    <id>tag:www.personal.psu.edu,2010:/erh5000/blogs/portfolio//31529.297404</id>

    <published>2010-10-12T14:35:14Z</published>
    <updated>2010-11-11T16:58:19Z</updated>

    <summary>I have been using the iPad for a few weeks, and have discovered some tips for using it more effectively. A few weeks ago, the iPad wouldn&apos;t turn on for me. I slightly panicked, wondering if it was somehow broken....</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Erica Hollis</name>
        
    </author>
    
    <category term="engl202c_ipad" label="Engl202c_ipad" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/">
        <![CDATA[<p>I have been using the iPad for a few weeks, and have discovered some tips for using it more effectively.  A few weeks ago, the iPad wouldn't turn on for me.  I slightly panicked, wondering if it was somehow broken.  I remembered that one time when I dropped it on the floor.  I tried holding in different buttons, but nothing worked.  Then I googled the problem and discovered the solution.  The iPad wasn't broken, it was completely turned off.  If this happens, just hold down the sleep/wake button on the top of the iPad for awhile, at least 10-15 seconds.  Then push the home button and the iPad should start up.  So if this ever happens to you, don't panic, just hold in the top button.<br /><br />I didn't really have many other tips for using the iPad, so I opened Pages to see if anything would come to mind.  I remembered that I used the header and footer to type my resume, and it was useful to just double tap the header to edit it.  Using the header and footer can help format your resume or document, if you want some things to line up to the left and others to the right.  For example, I used it to put my current address on the left, permanent address on the right, and name in the middle.<br /><br />Also, regarding Pages, I noticed that they added a word count.  This is something that I had complained about in a previous post, since it was lacking.  It is nice to see that the developers are adding new and useful features to the Pages application.  I think that Pages has more room for more improvement, and will be interested to see if how they improve the application in the future. <br /><br /><br />- Posted using BlogPress from my iPad<br /></p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Review of the &apos;Cube&apos; Application</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/10/review-of-the-cube-application.html" />
    <id>tag:www.personal.psu.edu,2010:/erh5000/blogs/portfolio//31529.293781</id>

    <published>2010-10-05T00:36:57Z</published>
    <updated>2010-10-05T01:41:08Z</updated>

    <summary>I downloaded the &apos;Cube&apos; application for the iPad about a week ago. Cube is a time and expense tracker that could be very useful to a business man or woman. The app is free but you can pay for an...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Erica Hollis</name>
        
    </author>
    
    <category term="engl202c_ipad" label="Engl202c_ipad" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/">
        <![CDATA[<p>I downloaded the 'Cube' application for the iPad about a week ago.  Cube is a time and expense tracker that could be very useful to a business man or woman.  The app is free but you can pay for an upgraded version. </p>

<p>I have been using mostly for the Cube for the calender.  The iPad comes with a calender, but I like the Cube calender much better.  To add a new entry, hit the plus sign in the upper right corner.  You can choose to add a time entry, expense, event, task, project, or client.  </p>

<p>The home page gives the day, name, and time of all your entries.  The app keeps track of the names of all your previous entries so that you can just click on it instead of re-typing every time, which is convenient.  I have found it kind of annoying to add a new name, because I always try to type the name into the search box.  This does not work: you have to click 'create new.'  So I automatically type the name into the search box, realize this does not work, click 'create new,' and then have to retype it.</p>

<p>There are two other useful buttons on the top left hand side.  The first shows a monthly calender, with details at the bottom.  You can choose to view current tasks, projects, clients, or tags.  The second is a bar graph.  This shows monthly weekly, or yearly bar graphs of your entries. It looks like this:</p>

<p><span class="mt-enclosure mt-enclosure-image" style="display: inline;"><a href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/photo.PNG"><img alt="photo.PNG" src="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/assets_c/2010/10/photo-thumb-800x1066-150977.png" width="800" height="1066" class="mt-image-center" style="text-align: center; display: block; margin: 0 auto 20px;" /></a></span></p>

<p>Each color represents a a different task for that day.You can click on one to see more details.  The calender that comes with the iPad is dull and boring.  Cube has a more interesting layout.  Also, cube has the extra features of expense tracking and a list of clients.  This application is useful for those with a busy calender because you can instantly add events or expenses without having to turn on a computer.</p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>A comment on the Doodle Buddy</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/09/a-comment-on-the-doodle-buddy.html" />
    <id>tag:www.personal.psu.edu,2010:/erh5000/blogs/portfolio//31529.290089</id>

    <published>2010-09-28T01:38:15Z</published>
    <updated>2010-09-28T02:12:15Z</updated>

    <summary>I enjoyed a post my classmate Cassandra Osterhoud recently posted called &quot;The Doodle Buddy&quot;: http://www.personal.psu.edu/cao5026/blogs/techwriting/2010/09/the-doodle-buddy.html Cassandra makes some interesting points that have opened up my mind about a use of the iPad in the working environment. When I first got...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Erica Hollis</name>
        
    </author>
    
    <category term="engl202c_ipad" label="Engl202c_ipad" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/">
        <![CDATA[<p>I enjoyed a post my classmate Cassandra Osterhoud recently posted called "The Doodle Buddy": </p>

<p>http://www.personal.psu.edu/cao5026/blogs/techwriting/2010/09/the-doodle-buddy.html</p>

<p>Cassandra makes some interesting points that have opened up my mind about a use of the iPad in the working environment.  When I first got the iPad, I downloaded a drawing app. I forget what it was called; I deleted it because I found it very hard to draw with.  I decided that drawing on the iPad was not easy and dismissed the idea.  After reading this blog post, I was intrigued and downloaded Doodle Buddy.  </p>

<p>I was actually impressed with Doodle Buddy.  I find it easy to use and draw with, especially after the bad experience with the previous application.  I agree that this app could be useful in a corporate setting.  Cassandra sold me with her point on how some things could be easier, such as drawing circles that would be difficult in Excel.</p>

<p>I have wondered how the iPad will be incorporated into the corporate environment.  This app could be very useful in many fields.  Besides Cassandra's examples, it could be used in the web design field.  Web designing often begins with a rough sketch of the layout of the website.  The web designer could sketch the layout on Doodle Buddy and then email it to all involved in the site.  Others could then edit it and email it back, adding convenience to the process.  This is just one example of how this application could make tasks electronic that normally would be done on paper.</p>

<p>One feature of this application that I've found impressive is that you can edit any saved photos on you have on the iPad, you don't have to start from scratch in the app.  There is a small selection of clip art that comes with it as well.  One criticism that I have of the application is that if you accidentally leave the app, it does not save what you were working on.  This could be frustrating and embarrassing if you are working with clients.  If you accidentally hit the 'home' button, a box should pop up that asks if you want to save your work so that you don't lose it.  </p>

<p>Other than that, I agree that this application could be useful in many ways in the working environment.  I would like to thank Cassandra for sharing her thoughts of the app!<br />
</p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Internships</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/09/internships.html" />
    <id>tag:www.personal.psu.edu,2010:/erh5000/blogs/portfolio//31529.283906</id>

    <published>2010-09-21T01:51:21Z</published>
    <updated>2010-09-21T02:33:21Z</updated>

    <summary>I would highly recommend internships to anyone in a technical field, or in any field. The economy isn&apos;t doing great, and an internship will give a student an edge when graduating. It will give you experience in a professional environment...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Erica Hollis</name>
        
    </author>
    
    <category term="engl202c_ipad" label="Engl202c_ipad" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/">
        <![CDATA[<p>I would highly recommend internships to anyone in a technical field, or in any field.  The economy isn't doing great, and an internship will give a student an edge when graduating.  It will give you experience in a professional environment related to your field.</p>

<p>Personally, I wanted to intern as soon as possible.  I took a few years off after high school working mindless jobs, and couldn't wait to work a job where I have to use my mind.  I got an internship last summer and still work there part-time.</p>

<p>It is nice to see that I actually use what I've learned in classes.  And it's nice to actually get paid for it.  I've learned a lot in my internship, and find that I have much more motivation to learn in a work environment, where as in school I have to push myself more.</p>

<p>I've learned a lot about technical writing in my internship.  I've read a lot of different kind of documents online to figure out how to solve problems, such as blogs, forums, and tutorials.  As far as writing goes, I communicate to others mostly through email.  Sometimes it can be challenging to figure out how to properly word emails, especially when emailing superiors.  Sometimes I have to put a little thought into it. </p>

<p>Here is a link to writing effective emails at work:</p>

<p>http://jerz.setonhill.edu/writing/etext/e-mail.htm</p>

<p> Lastly, I've written documents for my job, including instruction guides, taking notes for other employees, and programming code.  I feel that the classes at Penn State have been very helpful in my job, and this has motivated me to learn as much as a can in the classes I am taking now.  The internship has also piqued my interest in this technical writing course, because I see how important technical communication is.  </p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Using the iPad </title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/09/using-the-ipad.html" />
    <id>tag:www.personal.psu.edu,2010:/erh5000/blogs/portfolio//31529.279452</id>

    <published>2010-09-13T00:38:54Z</published>
    <updated>2010-09-13T01:30:35Z</updated>

    <summary>Last week I gave an overview on the iPad, including my initial impression of Pages. This week I would like to further comment on using Pages and iAnnotate PDF to write or to edit a document. When using Pages to...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Erica Hollis</name>
        
    </author>
    
    <category term="engl202c_ipad" label="Engl202c_ipad" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/">
        <![CDATA[<p>Last week I gave an overview on the iPad, including my initial impression of Pages.  This week I would like to further comment on using Pages and iAnnotate PDF to write or to edit a document.  When using Pages to write a document, I did not have much trouble.  I could easily cut and paste text and the spell check is helpful.  I did have other resources open on my laptop to look at while I was typing, such as the document I was critiquing  and the assignment sheet.  I did this because I find it more convenient than switching between different screens on the iPad.  I think I could have solved this problem if I had put the assignment sheet and document I was critiquing as desktop icons.  A user of the iPad could probably get more convenience out of it, as far as switching between different windows or apps, if they organize their desktop to suit them.</p>

<p>Screenshot from iAnnotate:</p>

<p><span class="mt-enclosure mt-enclosure-image" style="display: inline;"><img alt="iAnnotate.jpeg" src="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/iAnnotate.jpeg" width="120" height="160" class="mt-image-none" style="" /></span></p>

<p><br />
Besides Pages, I used iAnnotate PDF to edit a fellow classmate's paper.  The tools I used were highlighting text and inserting a comment.  I found that when highlighting text, it would highlight more text than what I wanted.  I would then have to hit the checkmark, hit the text again, hit the 'x', select "delete," and try again.  This would happen almost every time.  One cannot use this highlighting tool in haste, but should take their time and be very careful in order to avoid this.  Overall, the more I use these apps, the more I get used to it.  When i just now switched over from typing in the iPad to typing this blog on my laptop, I put my finger on the laptop screen, pointing to the text I wanted to delete; I forgot that I wasn't using a touch screen anymore!</p>

<p> </p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>First impressions of the iPad</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/09/first-impressions-of-the-ipad.html" />
    <id>tag:www.personal.psu.edu,2010:/erh5000/blogs/portfolio//31529.273576</id>

    <published>2010-09-07T15:02:08Z</published>
    <updated>2010-09-07T15:22:48Z</updated>

    <summary>I was excited to try out this iPad thing. I&apos;ve never owned an ipod or an iphone, but always heard about these cool apps for them. So when I got the ipad I went online, googled the best free apps,...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Erica Hollis</name>
        
    </author>
    
    <category term="engl202c_ipad" label="Engl202c_ipad" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/">
        <![CDATA[<pre>I was excited to try out this iPad thing.  I've never owned an <br />ipod or an iphone, but always heard about these cool apps for <br />them.  So when I got the ipad I went online, googled the best <br />free apps, and downloaded the ones that looked interesting.  <br />I download iBooks along with some free books.  I like iBooks - <br />the way it's laid out so you can see two pages at once, way you <br />can click on a chapter in the table of contents, and the way <br />that when you turn the pages it looks realistic.  I know there <br />are a few other features like text highlighting that I haven't <br />tried out yet.  <br /><br />I also downloaded a few games, some news apps, and some social <br />networking apps.  I use these when I'm bored, or when eating <br />lunch.  Lastly, I downloaded an app I like called eyewitness.  <br />It displays a picture every day from around the world, usually<br />related to some notable event.  The reason I like it is because <br />the pictures look amazing on the ipad, and sometimes evoke <br />emotions. The video and picture quality on the iPad is excellent.<br /><br />Overall, using Pages to write documents works well, except that <br />it only has a limited amount of features.  So far I've noticed <br />that it seems to be missing a word count, something that can be <br />very handy when writing assignments for school.  Using the <br />external keyboard with the iPad is very helpful, but I would <br />prefer to type some documents on my laptop, because the mouse <br />is convenient.  I may only be saying this because I'm not <br />completely used to the touch screen yet.<br /><br />I like that the iPad is small enough and light enough to carry <br />around, yet big enough to see everything on the screen.  I <br />believe it could be extremely useful on the go, but at home a <br />laptop or desktop computer may be more convenient.  One huge <br />perk for me about the iPad is that it is very fast (except on <br />the Penn State network it seems).  It turns on instantly, and <br />most apps load almost instantly.  Also, the ipad automatically <br />saves everything, such as webpages and documents on the pages <br />app.  This, along with the speed, makes it easy to go in between <br />different windows.  The touch screen works great, I've hardly had <br />any problems.  I've never owned a touch screen phone, but when <br />I've tried to use my friends' touch screen phones, I had trouble <br />getting it to do what I wanted.  This is definitely not the case <br />with the iPad, probably partly because it is much larger than a <br />phone.  Further more, the battery is great and very long lasting.  <br />Lastly, I enjoy the coolness aspect of the iPad.  I like <br />scrolling objects across the screen with my finger, it's fun!<br /> </pre> ]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>About me</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/08/about-me-1.html" />
    <id>tag:www.personal.psu.edu,2010:/erh5000/blogs/portfolio//31529.266616</id>

    <published>2010-08-27T21:38:33Z</published>
    <updated>2010-08-27T21:40:53Z</updated>

    <summary><![CDATA[I am a junior at Penn State University.&nbsp; I am majoring in computer science with a minor in mathematics.&nbsp; I enjoy what I am learning about because it challenges me and involves problem solving and logic, which I like.&nbsp; When...]]></summary>
    <author>
        <name>Erica Hollis</name>
        
    </author>
    
    <category term="engl202c_ipad" label="Engl202c_ipad" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/">
        <![CDATA[I am a junior at Penn State University.&nbsp; I am majoring in computer
science with a minor in mathematics.&nbsp; I enjoy what I am learning about
because it challenges me and involves problem solving and logic,
which I like.&nbsp; When working on writing assignments, I usually write on
my laptop or on a school computer, rather than by hand.&nbsp; Some students
spend hours doing schoolwork at the library, while some prefer to work
at home while having 'white noise' such as the television in the
background.&nbsp; I typically mix it up, doing some work at school, and then
doing some in the evenings at home. I get more done when I do
schoolwork at school or in a cafe, rather than at my house, where there
are too many distractions.&nbsp; Even though I know that I am more
productive working outside of home, on some days after classes I just
want to go home and relax for an hour before starting on homework. ]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

</feed>
