<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Erica Hollis' Portfolio: Comments</title>
    <link>http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Latest comments for Erica Hollis' Portfolio</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2010 09:31:56 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>http://www.movabletype.org/?v=4.34-en</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>

    <item>
      <title>Comment on "Internships"</title>
      <link>http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/09/internships.html#comments</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I've never interned before but it's mostly because I don't know what to expect in such environment.  It's reassuring to know that some of the skills and knowledge we obtain in our classes are definitely useful and applicable in the real world.  I find that writing effective emails also extends to writing them to advisers and professors.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- Michelle Yoo&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">comment111858@http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 10:54:35 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Comment on "iPad - pros and cons"</title>
      <link>http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/11/ipad---pros-and-cons.html#comments</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I also think the iPad is much more convenient to carry around school, especially if it eliminates the lugging around of those heavy hardcover school books.  I actually bought two books for my science classes and it is so much easier carrying them to class and being able to reference them during lectures.  As for writing, however, I am completely with you that Microsoft Word is much better and easier to use.  The iPad is not writer friendly which is why I prefer to use a laptop for writing assignments over the iPad.  Also I might have to try using the calendar like you do.  I need something like that to get a little more organized.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- MIke Randall&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">comment111783@http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 02:55:04 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Comment on "iPad Report"</title>
      <link>http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/11/ipad-report.html#comments</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I get the same problem with Angel, but I discovered that if you orient your screen in the portrait view, you can pretty much see everything on the page (unless the page is extremely long). I would agree with the Wifi function of the iPad as well - it's not as strong as I hoped and it often drops signals. For the email, I believe that if you use POP3 for mail, the mail programs don't synchronize with each other. However, if you use IMAP, the mail programs synchronize with each other (at least for me).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- Robert Bai&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">comment111767@http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 01:42:07 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Comment on "iPad - pros and cons"</title>
      <link>http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/11/ipad---pros-and-cons.html#comments</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I definitely agree with you that using the Pages app in the iPad is easier for designing documents and putting in shapes and graphics. I really liked using pages on the iPad for the Internet resource guide for the ease of designing documents. But for typing up documents Microsoft Word is so much more efficient than the iPad its ridiculous. I think you're spot on with how hard it is to get used to the on screen keyboard of the iPad after using an external keyboard for so long.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- Jake Arnold&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">comment111720@http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 23:09:28 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Comment on "First impressions of the iPad"</title>
      <link>http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/09/first-impressions-of-the-ipad.html#comments</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I totally know how you felt when you first got the iPad.  The only Apple device I own is an iPod and it is no where near as advanced in technology as the iPad. Instead of going to Google and searching free apps, I went to the app store on the iPad and searched free apps there. One game you should look into is the &quot;Words with Friends&quot; app.  It's like scrabble, and I am addicted to it!  As for convenience, I couldn't agree more!! That's my favorite thing about the device.  It's size, weight and speedy internet access (Minus the PSU wireless network) make it a great on-the-go device!  &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- JANET  LIEB&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">comment111488@http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 13:44:30 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Comment on "Internships"</title>
      <link>http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/09/internships.html#comments</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sounds like some great experiences!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dennis Jerz's blog is wonderful (the blog you link to). He's also, coincidentally, teaching with an iPad this term (Seton Hill is doing a much larger project with iPads).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- Michael J. Faris&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">comment098353@http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2010 18:09:14 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Comment on "First impressions of the iPad"</title>
      <link>http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/2010/09/first-impressions-of-the-ipad.html#comments</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Great post, Erica. I think the distinctions between the iPad and other computing devices is something that is going to be of great interest throughout the term — in fact, some are arguing that the iPad isn't a &quot;computing device&quot; so much as a toy. And I guess we'll be testing that claim in many ways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your comment about Pages is right on. It's going to be interesting to explore the options and limitations in Pages.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- Michael J. Faris&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">comment092624@http://www.personal.psu.edu/erh5000/blogs/portfolio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2010 09:31:56 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
